What do you recommend to people that are trying
to get that funding for their ideas to build companies?
Well, it always helps to have
something demonstrable and not just an idea.
Ideas are really difficult to get funded.
And if you can build something that's
even just a sample or especially an attack,
something that you can demonstrate, I
mean, that goes a long, long way.
There's an old expression that was
founded in the 70s, the expression,
and it happened to do with
all these advertising companies were creating,
I think it was called the dog food
wars, where they're creating all these different dog foods.
And they spent all this money
and they put them on television.
But it turns out the dogs
just didn't like the dog food.
And it didn't matter how great the
advertising was or how flashy it was.